mccainblogette.com 2012-05-24

# McCainBlogette.com - The Official Site of Meghan McCain

## Summary

Your privacy is very important to us. By using http://mccainblogette.com \- you are agreeing to the underlying Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes EQAL's use of personally identifiable information ("PII"-- your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number) that Members voluntarily provide to EQAL when they register for an account or otherwise provide PII to EQAL through your use of Website. Website is a general audience service and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.

## Amendments

From time to time EQAL may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of Website, or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting by EQAL. Your continued use of Website after EQAL posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If EQAL materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

When EQAL collects PII from you it is because you are voluntarily providing that information through your use of Website or submitting PII to us in order to register as a Member. In addition, EQAL collects other non-PII including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type. This data is used to manage and improve Website, track usage, and for security purposes. Members may also choose to provide or store non-PII information in their account, including but not limited to date of birth, interests, hobbies, lifestyle choices, groups with whom they are affiliated (schools, companies), videos and/or pictures, private messages, bulletins or personal statements (collectively "Profile Information"). The Information in a Member's account is provided at his or her sole discretion.

Members can change their PII and Profile Information at any time and can control how other Members and EQAL communicate with them by controlling their account settings, available within the "Edit Profile" section of the Member's profile page on any website operated by EQAL. Cookies are small bits of information that EQAL places on your computer. EQAL uses cookies to identify your Internet browser, store preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on Website. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services.

## Aggregated Statistics

EQAL may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors on the Website. (E.g., monitoring the most popular sites on Website to help identify spam). EQAL may display this information publicly or provide it to others. We will not disclose your PII unless otherwise indicated below.

## Advertisements

Third party advertisements displayed on Website by site owners may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers (known as "third party cookies"). EQAL does not control these third party cookies and Users of Website should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on customized advertising on EQAL. A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. EQAL may allow third party pixel tags to be present on Website for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on Website.

When you voluntarily provide PII to EQAL, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses EQAL will make of the information to the extent it is being used in a manner that differs from what is allowed pursuant to this Privacy Policy.

## 3rd Party Websites

Website may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Website may also carry advertisements from other companies. EQAL is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with Website or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once you leave Website via such a link (e.g., to sites such as [http://www.youtube.com](http://www.youtube.com/)), access a third party application (such as widgets) or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

Advertisements placed on the Website by a site owner may also be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect non-PII about your visit to or use of EQAL Service, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please click here.

Third party applications (such as widgets) created by third party developers may also be available on Website. Third party applications are small bits of software, often with interactivity, that can be installed into Members' profiles or shared with other Users. However, EQAL does not control the third party developers, and cannot dictate their actions. When a Member engages with a third party application, that Member is interacting with the third party developer, not with EQAL. EQAL encourages Members not to provide PII to the third party's application unless the Member knows the party with whom it is interacting.

## Use of Personally-Identifying Information

EQAL will only use the PII you provide under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If EQAL obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy.

## Member Search

In order to locate other EQAL Members that you may already know in the physical world, EQAL allows Users to search for Members using Registration PII (i.e., full name or email address). EQAL also allows Users to browse for certain Profile Information in order to help connect with Members. EQAL may also enable Members to publicly display some Registration PII as an element of their Profile Information if they choose to do so via a profile setting under "Edit Profile." Search engines may index the portion of a Member's profile (including the Profile Information it contains) that is publicly displayed.

## Promotional Materials

If you have consented to receive promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications from EQAL, EQAL may periodically use your email address to send you such materials related to Website, as applicable. If you want to stop receiving such materials from EQAL, you can access the "Edit Profile" section on your profile page within any website operated by EQAL for which you have subscribed or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

EQAL employees, agents and contractors must have a business reason to obtain access to your PII. EQAL may share your PII with those who help us manage or provide EQAL Service' information activities (for example, message board administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses, data processing), or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes.

## Disclosure

At EQAL's sole discretion, your PII may be shared with the third party owner or co-owner(s) of the website(s) which you join that is/are built on Website or one of its affiliated or related entities, in which case all PII will be subject to that entity or entities then applicable Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use, copies of which can be found at the owner's or co-owner(s)'s website.

There may be instances when EQAL may access or disclose PII, Profile Information or non-PII without providing you a choice in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of EQAL, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of Users of Website or members of the public including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if EQAL sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, EQAL may transfer your PII to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

When a Member who is located in the European Union chooses to post Profile Information that will be publicly disclosed, that Member is responsible for ensuring that such information conforms to all local data protection laws. EQAL is not responsible under the EU local data protection laws for Member-posted information.

## Security

EQAL uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII and credit card information (if applicable) in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, EQAL uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

Whenever possible, EQAL Members may review the Registration PII we maintain about them in our records. We will take reasonable steps to correct any PII a Member informs us is incorrect. If you are a Member, you can view and change your Registration PII, Member preferences and Profile Information by logging into your account and navigating to the "Edit Profile" section on your profile page. If you ask EQAL to stop using your PII, EQAL will honor that request while retaining any record of your PII that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law.

If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or EQAL's collection and use of your PII please email 

or write to us at

Privacy, EQAL, Inc.  
5250 Lankershim Blvd., Suite 720  
North Hollywood, CA 91601  
Attn: Paras Maniar
